dateyard.com 2018-12-13

# partner.dateyard.com | The dating affiliate program

We respect the privacy of every person who registers with or visits DATEYARD’s website and/or uses the services made available by us from the DATEYARD website (the “DATEYARD Service”) and we are committed to ensuring a safe online experience. 

* * *

### 1 PURPOSE OF THIS NOTICE 

This privacy notice explains our approach to any personal information that you might supply to us (or that might be collected from you) in connection with your use of the DATEYARD Service and sets out your rights in respect of DATEYARD’s processing of your personal information. For more information click here. 

* * *

### 2 WHO ARE WE AND WHAT DO WE DO? 

The DATEYARD Service is operated by dateyard AG (“DATEYARD”) whose principal activities include operating a centralised platform for a network of online dating sites which enable Users to create their own dating profiles and contact other Users of the platform or any of our additional platforms that we operate. Please be aware that when you create a dating profile on any of the platforms operated by DATEYARD, your profile will also be publicly available to Users of our additional platforms. For more information click here. 

* * *

### 3 HOW TO CONTACT US? 

If you have any questions about this privacy, please contact us by: 

• sending an email to support@datehelpdesk.com; 

• writing to us at dateyard AG, Rothusstrasse 23, 6331 Hünenberg, Switzerland 

* * *

### 4 WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND HOW DO WE COLLECT IT? 

Our primary goal in collecting personal information from you is to give you a customised experience while allowing us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs. In order to do so personal information may be collected from you in the following ways: 

→ Information you voluntarily provide to us. For more information click here. 

→ Information we collect through your use of the DATEYARD Service. For more information click here. 

* * *

### 5 HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION? 

We collect and use your personal information to operate the DATEYARD Service efficiently and to deliver you the very best service. In particular, we may use your personal information for the following purposes: 

→ Provision of the DATEYARD Service. For more information click here. 

→ Service administration. For more information click here. 

→ User Data Analysis. For more information click here. 

→ Internal record keeping and legal compliance. For more information click here

→ Marketing by third parties. For more information click here. 

→ Sharing information with third party processors. For more information click here. 

→ Sharing information with professional advisors & potential purchasers. For more information click here. 

* * *

### 6 HOW DO WE OBTAIN YOUR CONSENT? 

Where use of your personal information by us requires your consent, you can provide such consent: 

• at the time we collect your personal information following the instructions provided; or 

• by informing DATEYARD by e-mail or post using the [LINK SUPPORT]contact details set out in this Privacy Notice. 

* * *

### 7 USE OF COOKIES 

The DATEYARD Service may use certain cookies, pixels, beacons, log files and other technologies of which you should be aware. Please see our Cookie Policy to find out more about the cookies we use and how to manage and delete cookies. 

* * *

### 8 THIRD PARTY LINKS AND SERVICES 

The DATEYARD Service may contain links to third party websites and services. Please remember that when you use a link to go from DATEYARD to another website or you request a service from a third party, this privacy notice no longer applies. For more information click here. 

* * *

### 9 TRANSFERS OUTSIDE THE EEA 

We do not currently transfer your personal information outside of the EEA. 

* * *

### 10 HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR? 

We do not keep your personal information for any specific period but will not keep it for longer than is necessary for our purposes. 

In considering how long to keep it, we will take into account its relevance to our business and our legal and regulatory obligations. 

* * *

### 11 CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION 

We are committed to keeping the personal information you provide us secure and we will take reasonable precautions to protect your personal information from loss, misuse or alteration. For more information click here. 

* * *

### 12 HOW TO ACCESS YOUR INFORMATION AND YOUR OTHER RIGHTS? 

You have the following rights in relation to the personal information we hold about you: 

• Your right of access. For more information click here. 

• Your right to rectification. For more information click here. 

• Your right to erasure. For more information click here. 

• Your right to restrict processing. For more information click here. 

• Your right to data portability. For more information click here. 

• Your right to object. For more information click here. 

• Your rights in relation to automated decision-making and profiling. For more information click here. 

• Your right to withdraw consent. For more information click here. 

• Your right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority. For more information click here. 

* * *

### 13 CHANGE TO THIS PRIVACY NOTICE 

We may make changes to this privacy notice from time to time. For more information click here. 

Last Updated December 2017
